Guide to the Washington State Federation of Teachers Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Washington State Federation of Teachers records, 1937-2006; 2201-001; 20 cubic feet (20 boxes)
  - WASHINGTON STATE FEDERATION OF TEACHERS RECORDS, RECORD GROUP 1 (Box-folder 1/1-20/2)
    - CONVENTION AND CONFERENCE RECORDS, 1945-2005; SERIES VII (Box-folder 9/10-11/6)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1973 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1974 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers convention packet, 1974 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1975 (Box-folder 10/20)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention election of officers, 1975 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention -- Part 1 of 2, 1976 (Box-folder 10/22)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention -- Part 2 of 2, 1976 (Box-folder 10/23)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention credentials, 1976 (Box-folder 10/24)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention -- Part 1 of 2, 1977 (Box-folder 10/25)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention -- Part 2 of 2, 1977 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention, 1978 (Box-folder 10/27)
      - Washington State Federation of Teachers Convention credentials and ballots, 1979 (Box-folder 10/28)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention, 1986 (Box-folder 10/29)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention minutes, 1989 (Box-folder 10/30)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention resolutions, 1995 (Box-folder 10/31)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention, 1996 (Box-folder 10/32)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers convention packet, 1996 (Box-folder 10/33)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention, 1997 (Box-folder 10/34)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention, 1998 (Box-folder 10/35)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention resolutions, 1998 (Box-folder 10/36)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention, 1999 (Box-folder 10/37)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention, 2000 (Box-folder 10/38)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention minutes, 2001 (Box-folder 10/39)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention resolutions report, 2003 (Box-folder 10/40)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention resolutions, 2005 (Box-folder 10/41)
      - Northwest Community and Technical College Conference, 1993 (Box-folder 10/42)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Classified Workers Conference, 1993 (Box-folder 10/43)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers / Association for Higher Education: Higher Education Conference, 1997 (Box-folder 10/44)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers / Association for Higher Education: Higher Education Conference, 1999 (Box-folder 10/45)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Leadership Conference, 1991 (Box-folder 10/46)
      - Washington Federation of Teachers Leadership Conference, 1992 (Box-folder 10/47)
      - Union Leadership Institute / Washington, 1994 (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Union Leadership Institute / Washington, 1995 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Union Leadership Institute / Washington, 1996 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Union Leadership Institute / Washington, 1997 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Union Leadership Institute / Washington, 1998 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Washington State Labor Council Industrial Union Section 11th annual meeting, 1968 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - SUBJECT FILES, 1943-2006; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 11/7-17/28)
      - Aberdeen and Hoquiam, 1946 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Aberdeen Federation of Teachers, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Aberdeen strike, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 11/9)
      - Academic freedom, loyalty oaths, c. 1966 (Box-folder 11/10)
      - The Adjunct Advocate, 1992 (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Affirmative action / I-200, 1998 (Box-folder 11/12)
      - AFL-CIO Public Employee Department, 1976 (Box-folder 11/13)
      - American Federation of Teachers and National Education Association merger plans, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 11/14)
      - American Federation of Teachers - National Education Association merger, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 11/15)
      - American Federation of Teachers - National Education Association merger talks, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 11/16)
      - American Federation of Teachers / National Education Association project file, 1998-2007 (Box-folder 11/17)
      - American Federation of Teachers Washington Executive Board strategic planning, 2002 (Box-folder 11/18)
      - American Federation of Teachers, 1946-1953 (Box-folder 11/19)
      - American Federation of Teachers. Colleges and Universities Committee -- Part 1 of 3, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 11/20)
      - American Federation of Teachers. Colleges and Universities Committee -- Part 2 of 3, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 11/21)
      - American Federation of Teachers. Colleges and Universities Committee -- Part 3 of 3, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 11/22)
      - American Federation of Teachers: David Selden, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 11/23)
      - American Federation of Teachers grants, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 11/24)
      - Agency shop, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 11/25)
      - Agency shop / fair share payers, 1986 (Box-folder 11/26)
      - Auburn, 1946 (Box-folder 11/27)
      - Bakke decision, 1977 (Box-folder 11/28)
      - Bellevue Community College, 1972 (Box-folder 11/29)
      - Frank Behm notes, Undated, 1947 (Box-folder 11/30)
      - Binding arbitration: AG opinion, 1969 (Box-folder 11/31)
      - Blue Cross / Washington Education Association, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 11/32)
      - Bremerton Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers Local 336, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 11/33)
      - Buckley, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 11/34)
      - Building Service Employees, 1947 (Box-folder 11/35)
      - Bus driver assault bill, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 11/36)
      - Cascadia Community College, 2002 (Box-folder 11/37)
      - Central Washington University, 1976 (Box-folder 11/38)
      - Central Washington University Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers Local 3231, 1975 (Box-folder 11/39)
      - Centralia and Chehalis, 1946 (Box-folder 11/40)
      - Charter schools, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 11/41)
      - Citizens for Fair School Funding, 1976 (Box-folder 11/42)
      - Civil rights: American Federation of Teachers Civil Rights Committee, Undated (Box-folder 11/43)
      - Civil rights / student housing, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 11/44)
      - Classified employee planning meeting, 1997 (Box-folder 11/45)
      - Classified employee survey, 1989 (Box-folder 11/46)
      - Classified project, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 11/47)
      - Classified Public Employees Association, 1978 (Box-folder 11/48)
      - Collective bargaining, 1972 (Box-folder 11/49)
      - Collective bargaining in higher education: HB 59, 1977 (Box-folder 11/50)
      - Collective bargaining in higher education: legislation, 1978 (Box-folder 11/51)
      - Collective bargaining in higher education: SSB 2236, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 11/52)
      - Collective bargaining in higher education, 2002 (Box-folder 11/53)
      - Collective bargaining of fringe benefits, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 11/54)
      - Committee on Coordination of Labor, 1939 (Box-folder 11/55)
      - Committee on Political Education contribution thank-yous, 2000 (Box-folder 11/56)
      - Committee on Political Education endorsements, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 11/57)
      - Committee on Political Education committee and endorsements, 2006 (Box-folder 11/58)
      - Committee on Political Education pledge drive, 2005 (Box-folder 11/59)
      - Community College Council, 1985 (Box-folder 11/60)
      - Community College Council, 1986 (Box-folder 11/61)
      - Community College Innovative Educational Programs, 1972 (Box-folder 12/1)
      - Community College Legislative Council, 1972 (Box-folder 12/2)
      - Community College Legislative Council, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 12/3)
      - Proposed Community College legislative council, 1971 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Community college negotiations and tenure, 1967 (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Community college tenure / ESB 556, 1969 (Box-folder 12/6)
      - Constitutions of affiliates and others, Undated, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 12/7)
      - Constitutions: examples and models, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Consultants' Advisory Council, 1971 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Contract proposals, 1977 (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Contracts: examples and models, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Coordinating Council for Justice Under State Taxation, 1969 (Box-folder 12/12)
      - Corrections -- HB 2010, 1995 (Box-folder 12/13)
      - Department of Corrections education programs, 1996 (Box-folder 12/14)
      - Counselor positions, Undated (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Daly case, Shelton Washington, 1965 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Decentralization workshop, 1969 (Box-folder 12/17)
      - Diablo Valley Education Project: teaching about war and peace, 1968 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - Discipline, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Dues problem: American Federation of Teachers, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Economic security workshop, 1972 (Box-folder 12.21)
      - Edmonds Community College classified employees, 1998 (Box-folder 12/22)
      - Edmonds Federation of Teachers, American Federation of Teachers Local 1690, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 12/23)
      - Education collective bargaining, 1974 (Box-folder 12/24)
      - Education conference attendee list, 1938 (Box-folder 12/25)
      - Educational accountability, 1972 (Box-folder 12/26)
      - Educational Services Registration Act, 1979 (Box-folder 12/27)
      - Election endorsements, 1965 (Box-folder 12/28)
      - Equity Campaign, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 12/29)
      - Equity Campaign, 2000 (Box-folder 12/30)
      - Ergonomics rule, 1999 (Box-folder 12/31)
      - Everett, 1969 (Box-folder 12/32)
      - Everett Community College Federation of Teachers American Federation of Teachers Local 1873, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 12/33)
      - Everett Federation of Teachers American Federation of Teachers Local 772, 1943-1976 (Box-folder 12/34)
      - Everett Federation of Teachers American Federation of Teachers Local 772 - part 1 of 2, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 12/35)
      - Everett Federation of Teachers American Federation of Teachers Local 772 - part 2 of 2, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 12/36)
      - Expenses, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 12/37)
      - Fifty percent bill, 1971 (Box-folder 12/38)
      - Governor's Task Force on Higher Education, 1996 (Box-folder 12/39)
      - H. D. Graves, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 12/40)
      - Green River Community College, 1975 (Box-folder 12/41)
      - Green River Community College collective bargaining campaign, 1972 (Box-folder 12/42)
      - Green River Community College Federation of Teachers election, 1972 (Box-folder 12/43)
      - Hawaii organizing campaign, 1972 (Box-folder 12/44)
      - Hawaii strike, 1973 (Box-folder 12/45)
      - Hawaii strike: press clippings, 1973 (Box-folder 12/46)
      - Keith Hoeller, 1996 (Box-folder 12/47)
      - House bill 764, 1973 (Box-folder 12/48)
      - Increment bill, 2006 (Box-folder 12/49)
      - Initiatives, 2000 (Box-folder 12/50)
      - Initiative 314, 1975 (Box-folder 12/51)
      - Inner cities schools, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Job sharing and tenure, 1992 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Ralph Johnson, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Joint Vocational Education - Vocational Rehabilitation Study Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - K-12 Council, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 13/5)
      - Labor support, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 13/6)
      - Legislation, 1943-1965 (Box-folder 13/7)
      - Legislation, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 13/8)
      - Legislation, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 13/9)
      - Legislation, 1973 (Box-folder 13/10)
      - Legislation, 1974 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - Legislation, 1975 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Legislation, 1976 (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Legislation, 1977 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Legislation, 1978 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - Legislation, 1980 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - Legislative activities, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 13/17)
      - Legislative issues, retirement, 1943-1947 (Box-folder 13/18)
      - Legislative issues, retirement: clippings, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Legislative issues, 1965 (Box-folder 13/20)
      - Legislative issues, 1995 (Box-folder 13/21)
      - Legislative issues, 1996 (Box-folder 13/22)
      - Legislative issues, 2001 (Box-folder 13/23)
      - Legislative issues, 2002 (Box-folder 13/24)
      - Legislative issues, 2003 (Box-folder 13/25)
      - Legislative issues, 2004 (Box-folder 13/26)
      - Legislative issues, 2005 (Box-folder 13/27)
      - Legislative Program Committee, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 13/28)
      - Legislative program planning, 1997 (Box-folder 13/29)
      - Legislative session, 1947 (Box-folder 13/30)
      - Legislative testimony, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Legislature candidates, 1996 (Box-folder 13/32)
      - Lewiston, 1946 (Box-folder 13/33)
      - Lobby Day, 1991 (Box-folder 13/34)
      - Lobby Day, 1992 (Box-folder 13/35)
      - Lobby Day, 1996 (Box-folder 13/36)
      - Lobby Day, 1997 (Box-folder 13/37)
      - Lobby Day, 1999 (Box-folder 13/38)
      - Lobbyist contract and reports, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 13/39)
      - Lobbyist reports, 1998 (Box-folder 13/40)
      - Lobbyist reporting forms, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13/41)
      - Local Union Recognition Program, 2005 (Box-folder 13/42)
      - Longview and Kelso, 1946 (Box-folder 13/43)
      - Marysville, 1946 (Box-folder 13/44)
      - Mercer Island, 1969 (Box-folder 13/45)
      - Merit pay for teachers, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 13/46)
      - Elmer Miller, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 13/47)
      - Montana, 1947 (Box-folder 13/48)
      - More Effective Schools Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 13/49)
      - Mount Vernon, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 13/50)
      - Mutual of Omaha, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13/51)
      - National Council of State Legislatures, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 13/52)
      - Negotiated agreements, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 13/53)
      - Sample agreements, Undated (Box-folder 13/54)
      - New faculty seminar, 2001 (Box-folder 13/55)
      - Northwest Part-time Instructors Association, 1972 (Box-folder 13/56)
      - Notes, Undated, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 13/57)
      - Olympia, 1949 (Box-folder 13/58)
      - Olympia, 1972 (Box-folder 13/59)
      - Olympia Vocational Technical Institute, 1973 (Box-folder 13/60)
      - Organizer's and Field Representative's reports, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 13/61)
      - Organizing and affiliation information, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 13/62)
      - Organizing materials and reports, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Organizing materials, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Organizing opportunities, 1996 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Organizing planning, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 14/4)
      - Organizing work, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Pacific Northwest Labor College, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Parochial school organizing, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - Part-time and contingent workers, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - Part-time Caucus, 1992 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - Part-time contract provisions, Community College System, 1998 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - Part-time disparity funding, 1997 (Box-folder 14/11)
      - Part-time dues, Undated (Box-folder 14/12)
      - Part-time equity, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - Part-time equity campaign, 1999 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - Part-time faculty, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 14/15)
      - Part-time faculty bills, 1996-2004 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - Part-time faculty survey, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - Part-time organizing project, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 14/18)
      - Part-time pro rata bill, 2000 (Box-folder 14/19)
      - Part-time rally, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14/20)
      - Part-time survey, 1999 (Box-folder 14/21)
      - Part-time Task Force, 1998 (Box-folder 14/22)
      - Part-time Task Force / Equity Campaign, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 14/23)
      - Part-time wages lawsuit, 1998 (Box-folder 14/24)
      - Harold Paschal, 1948 (Box-folder 14/25)
      - PEMCO, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 14/26)
      - Peninsula College, 1993 (Box-folder 14/27)
      - Pension legislation, 1995-2005 (Box-folder 14/28)
      - Pension reform legislation, 1976 (Box-folder 14/29)
      - Performance contracts, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 14/30)
      - Performance contracting, 1971 (Box-folder 14/31)
      - Personnel evaluations, 1970 (Box-folder 14/32)
      - Personnel files public disclosure, 1988 (Box-folder 14/33)
      - Pierce College Federation of Teachers American Federation of Teachers Local 4821, 1993 (Box-folder 14/34)
      - Pierce College proposals, 1999 (Box-folder 14/35)
      - Pierce County, 1947 (Box-folder 14/36)
      - Policy statements, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 14/37)
      - Policy statements, 1967 (Box-folder 14/38)
      - Political action workshop, Undated (Box-folder 14/39)
      - Port Orchard Federation of Teachers American Federation of Teachers Local 807, 1944-1982 (Box-folder 14/40)
      - Port Townsend, 1946 (Box-folder 14/41)
      - Portland, 1946 (Box-folder 14/42)
      - Post-tenure evaluation, 1993 (Box-folder 14/43)
      - Press clippings, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 14/44)
      - Press clippings -- Part 1 of 2, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 14/45)
      - Press clippings -- Part 2 of 2, 1964-1974 (Box-folder 14/46)
      - Press clippings -- Part 1 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14/47)
      - Press clippings -- Part 2 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14/48)
      - Press clippings, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 15/1)
      - Press clippings, 1978 (Box-folder 15/2)
      - Press clippings, 1979 (Box-folder 15/3)
      - Press clippings, 1980 (Box-folder 15/4)
      - Press releases, Undated, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 15/5)
      - Press releases, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 15/6)
      - Press releases, 1976 (Box-folder 15/7)
      - Press releases, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 15/8)
      - Private day care centers, 1974 (Box-folder 15/9)
      - Professional practices legislation, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 15/10)
      - Public Education Management Survey, 1976 (Box-folder 15/11)
      - Public employee collective bargaining, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 15/12)
      - Public employee collective bargaining, 1986 (Box-folder 15/13)
      - Public Employees Collective Bargaining Act, 1970 (Box-folder 15/14)
      - Public relations campaign, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 15/15)
      - Public School Employees of Washington case, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 15/16)
      - Public School Employees of Washington / Washington Federation of Teachers talks, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 15/17)
      - Publication information, Undated, 1946 (Box-folder 15/18)
      - Pullman, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 15/19)
      - Pupil discipline statutes and rules, 1976 (Box-folder 15/20)
      - Puyallup paraprofessionals, 1992 (Box-folder 15/21)
      - Rainier School Federation of Classified Instructors American Federation of Teachers Local 3340, 1975-1982 (Box-folder 15/22)
      - Raymond, 1946 (Box-folder 15/23)
      - Raymond Federation of Teachers, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 15/24)
      - Reasonable assurance bill, 1998 (Box-folder 15/25)
      - Referendum 55, 2004 (Box-folder 15/26)
      - Release time, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 15/27)
      - Renton, 1946 (Box-folder 15/28)
      - Renton Federation of Teachers, Undated (Box-folder 15/29)
      - Reports of officers and organizers, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 15/30)
      - Resolutions, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 15/31)
      - Restructuring task force, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 15/32)
      - Retiree organizing, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 15/33)
      - Retirement, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 15/34)
      - Retirement System rules, 1988 (Box-folder 15/35)
      - Richland, 1948 (Box-folder 15/36)
      - Running Start enrollment limitations, 1997 (Box-folder 15/37)
      - Salary schedules, 1958-1970 (Box-folder 15/38)
      - "Save Our Colleges" campaign, 1981 (Box-folder 15/39)
      - School decentralization, 1968 (Box-folder 15/40)
      - School Formula Committee, 1971 (Box-folder 15/41)
      - Seattle Community College District 6-year planning effort, 1972 (Box-folder 15/42)
      - Seattle Community College District Budget Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 15/43)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 15/44)
      - Seattle Community College District contract proposals, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 15/45)
      - Seattle Community College District negotiations (part 1 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 15/46)
      - Seattle Community College District negotiations (part 2 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 15/47)
      - Seattle Community College District negotiations (part 3 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 15/48)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers -- Part 1 of 3, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15/49)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers -- Part 2 of 3, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15/50)
      - Seattle Community College Federation of Teachers -- Part 3 of 3, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15/51)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, Local 200 American Federation of Teachers -- Part 1 of 3, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 16/1)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, Local 200 American Federation of Teachers -- Part 2 of 3, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 16/2)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, Local 200 American Federation of Teachers -- Part 3 of 3, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 16/3)
      - Seattle Federation of Teachers, Local 200 American Federation of Teachers, 1992 (Box-folder 16/4)
      - Seattle Public Schools, 1936-1964 (Box-folder 16/5)
      - School Employees' Retirement System and pension issues, 2000 (Box-folder 16/6)
      - Shoreline Community College agreement, 1975 (Box-folder 16/7)
      - Sick leave for part-time faculty, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 16/8)
      - South Kitsap School District, 1975 (Box-folder 16/9)
      - Spokane, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 16/10)
      - State-wide Bargaining Issues Task Force, 1998 (Box-folder 16/11)
      - State-wide community college salary study, 1969 (Box-folder 16/12)
      - Strike instructions and circulars, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 16/13)
      - Student American Federation of Teachers membership information, Undated (Box-folder 16/14)
      - Support Lawful Order Council, 1970 (Box-folder 16/15)
      - Surveys, Undated (Box-folder 16/16)
      - Tacoma / Dalton, 1946 (Box-folder 16/17)
      - Tacoma Association of Classroom Teachers, 1977 (Box-folder 16/18)
      - Tacoma Community College collective bargaining campaign, 1972 (Box-folder 16/19)
      - Tacoma Community College Federation of Teachers, 1980 (Box-folder 16/20)
      - Tacoma Community College: clippings, 1973 (Box-folder 16/21)
      - Tacoma Federation of Teachers, 1975 (Box-folder 16/22)
      - Tacoma paraprofessional negotiations (part 1 of 2), 1973 (Box-folder 16/23)
      - Tacoma paraprofessional negotiations (part 2 of 2), 1973 (Box-folder 16/24)
      - Tacoma Public Schools: the education crisis, 1969 (Box-folder 16/25)
      - Tacoma strike threat, 1972 (Box-folder 16/26)
      - Tax information, 1964 (Box-folder 16/27)
      - Taxation, 1947 (Box-folder 16/28)
      - Teachers' aides, 1967 (Box-folder 16/29)
      - Teaching assistant collective bargaining, 2001 (Box-folder 16/30)
      - Teaching assistant organizing, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 16/31)
      - Technical College Council, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 16/32)
      - Technology, 1997 (Box-folder 16/33)
      - Tenure, SB 5456, 1990 (Box-folder 16/34)
      - Faculty tenure, SHB 5878, 1993 (Box-folder 16/35)
      - Textbook costs, SSB 6699 and SHB 3087, 2006 (Box-folder 16/36)